Guide to the Julien Cornell Papers Relating to Ezra Pound
Beinecke Rare Book and Manuscript Library
- U. S. v. Ezra Pound Case File, Series II
  - OTHER CASE MATERIAL
    - Record of expenses related to the trial and receipts from the Irving Trust Company, 1946, n.d. (Box 3, Folder 101)
    - Notes, drafts, writings, 1947, n.d. (Box 3, Folder 102)
      Includes a statement by Bruno Fonzi about his experiences with Pound in Italy, "Breakfast with Ezra Pound," and an unsigned typescript of an article concerning Pound, "Shall it then be?"
    - Notes in Pound's hand (Box 3, Folder 103)
      Includes a typescript article about Pound from the Canton Repository, with Pound's ms. comments.
    - List of books in Mary Sinclair's estate with Pound's ms. selections. (Box 3, Folder 104)
    - Transcripts of Pound Rome Radio Broadcasts
      - Bound volume of transcripts: 1941-1942 Mar, [1946] (Box 4, Folder 105)
      - Bound volume of transcripts: 1942 Apr-Jul, [1946] (Box 4, Folder 106)
      - Bound volume of transcripts: 1942 Jul-1943, [1946] (Box 4, Folder 107)
      - Bound volume of transcripts: 1943 May-Jul, [1946] (Box 4, Folder 108)
- Restricted Fragile
  Conditions Governing Access
  Box 19: Restricted fragile material. Reference surrogates have been substituted in the main files. For further information consult the appropriate curator.
  - Box 1, folder 14 (Box 5, Folder 109)
  - Box 1, folder 22 (Box 5, Folder 110)
  - Box 1, folder 24 (Box 5, Folder 111)
  - Box 1, folder 25 (Box 5, Folder 112)
  - Box 1, folder 31 (Box 5, Folder 113)
  - Box 1, folder 36 (Box 5, Folder 114)
  - Box 1, folder 36 (Box 5, Folder 115)
  - Box 1, folder 37 (Box 5, Folder 116)
  - Box 1, folder 38 (Box 5, Folder 117)
  - Box 1, folder 40 (Box 5, Folder 118)
  - Box 2, folder 51 (Box 5, Folder 119)
  - Box 2, folder 55 (Box 5, Folder 120)
  - Box 2, folder 59 (Box 5, Folder 121)
  - Box 2, folder 66 (Box 5, Folder 122)
  - Box 2, folder 69 (Box 5, Folder 123)
  - Box 2, folder 79 (Box 5, Folder 124)
  - Box 3, folder 96 (Box 5, Folder 125)
  - Box 4, folder 99 (Box 5, Folder 126)
  - Box 4, folder 102 (Box 5, Folder 127)